Let me start with a little story. So,
I'm I'm 23 years old at this point. I
just quit my full-time job. I just
closed this deal with a client and I
deliver something and and he messages me
on Slack and he's like, "Hey, can we get
on a call?" And this is what he says to
me as soon as I hop on the Zoom. He
goes, "We are not getting the value that
we paid for." But I made three big
mistakes here. And that's pretty much
what I want to talk about today are
these three big mistakes. So the first
one is that what I built for him, the
personal assistant, was not the
constraint in his business. The second
one, I guess you guys saw the third one.
The second one is that I didn't choose a
KPI.
And the third one is that I guessed on
the price. So like I said, that's what I
want to talk about today.
So right now, I'm at this event in
Montenegro called Workless AI, and there
are a bunch of AI content creators, AI
experts, and a bunch of community
members. And on the main day, I closed
off the day with this presentation which
I'm about to share with you guys. So,
hope you guys enjoy. Hope you find it
insightful. I'll see you guys in there.
This is called Still Relevant Next Year.
And it's actually kind of funny because
last night I kind of switched up what I
was going to talk about a little bit
because yesterday in the VIP sections
and I talked to so many of you guys and
I just kind of had a feeling that this
would resonate a bit more because
whether you are I mean I think a lot of
you guys are building kind of like an AI
consultancy, an AI agency or working
with clients. Um, but even if you're
not, I think that this is the way that
you should be thinking about using AI
within your own business. And um, yeah.
So, let me just although also, um, I
hope this picture that's Montenegro,
right? Okay. That'd be awkward if it
wasn't. I I wasn't sure. It was codeex
threw it in there. So, good to know that
that's Montenegro. Okay, cool. So, start
with a little story. So, I'm I'm 23
years old at this point. I just quit my
full-time job. I just closed this deal
with a client and I deliver something
and and he messages me on Slack and he's
like, "Hey, can we get on a call?" And
this is what he says to me as soon as I
hop on the Zoom. He goes, "We are not
getting the value that we paid for." And
this really made me think because,
you know, I started to question like,
did I just make a huge mistake? Am I not
actually able to build these solutions?
Am I not going to turn this into a
business? And so I realized that the
reason that this happened was because,
well, first of all, I made this video
which went viral. It was like a personal
assistant. And so he saw that. Lots of
people saw that and they wanted this.
But I made three big mistakes here. And
that's pretty much what I want to talk
about today are these three big
mistakes. So the first one is
that what I built for him, the personal
assistant, was not the constraint in his
business. The second one, I guess you
guys saw the third one. The second one
is that I didn't choose a KPI.
And the third one is that I guessed on
the price. So like I said, that's what I
want to talk about today. I had a big
realization here before I started to
scale my business and I was doing
everything in the agency myself all the
way from the lead genen all the way to
the you know invoicing all of that kind
of stuff. I realized that our job is to
be the ones to diagnose and prove you
know it's one thing to just be kind of
like you take the ticket you develop
whatever they're asking for. You kind of
evolve from that and then you start to
be the doctor and you start to diagnose
the pain that they're feeling. But then
you're still not done yet because you
have to prove the value because if you
don't prove the value then how are you
going to win more business? And I've got
another quick story to tell you guys
about in just a sec. But first I wanted
to start off with if you guys don't know
me a little bit about my background. My
name is Nate. Graduated from the
University of Iowa in 2024 and I was
studying business analytics and
marketing. So don't come from a
technical background although I did work
with data quite a bit. So I've got a
good understanding of data which was
very helpful in automation. So can't lie
about that. Um, from there I graduated
and I was working at Goldman Sachs as an
analyst and I was automating a lot of
stuff. And what that helped me realize
was that automation is not new at all.
It feels new because the word AI has
been put in front of it. And that's what
a lot of business owners are kind of
waking up to. And it's funny because
when I first started running my agency,
I used to joke with my friends and you
know some of my my partners when I
started when I brought on some partners
that we're not even an AI agency. We are
a data infrastructure agency and then
after that we're just a boring
automation agency. And I think that's a
really good realization to have because
that
the whole reframe of diagnosing the
problem is that people might come to you
and they want an AI agent because they
saw a YouTube video that went viral or
because they saw something on LinkedIn,
but your job is to figure out what do
they actually need. Um,
and remember how I said the thing about
you have to prove the value. I was
building a lot of automations at Goldman
and actually you know that's on the next
slide I'll talk about that in a sec. um
sold my agency for sold my agency once
we scaled it past $100,000 a month. It
was purely because I was way more
passionate about education. Um but the
reason we were able to get to $100,000 a
month is because the minimum to work
with us was a $20,000 a month retainer.
And the only reason we were able to do
those retainers is because of this exact
kind of like three-step framework of
working with clients. Um I've got a
YouTube channel. It's pretty much the
top of funnel. That's where I am doing a
lot of the education. And then my free
community called a automation society is
where we try to get people into and try
to build community. So real quick, I
wanted to start off with like why did I
bring up the Goldman thing? What did
that teach me? Number one, like I said,
boring is beautiful. Deterministic
automations, they're easier to build.
They are easier to evaluate and they are
less risky ultimately because they're
deterministic. You know the inputs and
you know the outputs. Two is that big
companies I was, you know, hosting is
doing a lot of stuff with AI which is
which is awesome but typically when I've
worked with companies and when I was at
Goldman just kind of move slower they
have a lot of change management issues
and obviously in a or an institution
like Goldman in that type of vertical
there's a lot of regulation and then the
third thing is that you need to
spotlight your value. So quick story
here I remember I was building a lot of
automations like I said I built a few
like weekly report things. I built a few
dashboards and I was on a call with my
entire team. So probably 20 25 people
and I was showing them this automation,
you know, on a Zoom call. So your name
is right there under your face, right?
And I get off the call. It was also my
job to send out the meeting minutes,
which obviously we know AI can do now.
But I sent out the meeting minutes and I
got a response from one of the managers
that said, "Good job, Arthur." I'm like,
"Who is Arthur? My name is right there
and I sent you the meeting minutes." And
that just made me realize that if you're
not explaining to the business owner, to
the stakeholder what your automation
actually did, then it's hard to get
credit for it. So you could potentially
be in a situation where you're making
the business tens of thousands of
dollars, but they don't actually know
that or acknowledge that because you
didn't prove it. And it's not bragging,
it's just proving what your systems
actually did. So those are three big
lessons that I had that I tried to carry
with me through my AI automation agency
journey.
Now, think about it like this. So truly
the only way for a business to scale is
to remove constraints. And it's very
simple at a high level. Obviously
there's a lot of things that you know a
lot of nuance once you get into the
weeds of that but that's at the end of
the day if you want a business to scale
you have to remove constraints.
You might get a lot of people coming to
you like I did that says, "Hey, we need
an AI agent that does X, Y, and Z
because they saw a viral video because
their board is putting pressure on them
to have an AI strategy because their
competitors are posting on LinkedIn
saying, "Look at this AI agent that we
built that's doing all this for us." And
so that makes me feel like what they're
doing is they're actually just buying
relief. They're buying the ability to
say, "Yeah, we work with an AI agency.
Yeah, we have an AI strategy. We have
this agent going to production. We have
blah blah blah." But that's not really
what you're trying to provide. You're
not trying to provide relief. if you're
trying to provide real business value.
So, the whole idea is to reframe. I've
done
probably 300 or more discovery calls and
what I've realized is that they come to
you and they say something, but that's
almost never what they want. And so,
your job is to figure out why did they
book in the call? Because they booked in
for some reason, right? They had they're
feeling pain or they're feeling
pressure. And so, you have you have to
figure out what is that actual pain. You
kind of have to take a step back there.
There's pain somewhere and that is your
job. You are paid to solve the pain and
the more pain you can solve, the more
money that your business will make.
I think this might have might have died
on me. Okay, so the reason I put this up
there is because think about if you were
to work with an agency that was going to
help you run ads. It's super super
clear. Like you know what is your budget
for ads? $10,000 and you in a direct
correlation because of you ran those
ads, you made $50,000 in sales. That
like the agency doesn't even have to
prove that to you. It's very clear but
it's not super clear when it comes to
automation. So you have to make it
clear.
So those are the three things I want to
talk about right constraints KPIs stands
for key performance indicator and then
how do you actually price this stuff so
that you can clearly show this is how
much you paid and this is how much
you're going to make your business back.
Okay. So starting off with a constraint.
The only way for a business to scale is
to remove constraints to directly attack
them.
And at a very high level, your business
is either going to be supply constrained
or demand constrained. Meaning supply
constrained, too many customers coming
in and you cannot service them. Demand
constrained, you need business. You have
no people coming in. So I really like to
think of this as a pipe.
The water coming into your pipe is
revenue. It's cash flow. And you
obviously want that pipe to be clean, no
leaks, and you want lots of water to go
through. So the top image we see is a
pipe that has a clog in the middle. And
this is probably a supply constrained
business because they're having a lot of
water come through, but the water isn't
making it all the way to the end. Maybe
it's leaking out. It's not coming out
the other end of the pipe. The bottom
one is one where there's no water in the
pipe. And right now there's no clogs.
There probably are. There there always
more clogs. But right now this this
business on the bottom is demand
constrained and they need more water
inside their pipe.
So let me tell you another quick story.
I had a med spa owner that came to me
and she wanted a lead generation AI
agent. She wanted to make more money and
I saw the stat the other day. Um,
couldn't be outdated by now given how
fast the space moves. But the stat was
basically that over 50% of all AI
automations are like lead genen or sales
or marketing automations. And I think
that makes sense because what is the
pain a lot of us are feeling is that we
want to scale our monthly recurring
revenue. And usually the first thing you
think is like oh more leads, more
clients. But in this case, the med spa
owner wanted more leads. And when I
really tried to dig into the pain there
and figure out where the constraint was,
the constraint was, she ended up telling
me that they had lots of leads coming in
consistently, but what happened was they
weren't showing up to their
appointments. And then all of the people
that had showed up to an appointment,
there was no follow-up. So the LTV was
extremely low, meaning there was a
decent amount of water coming in the
pipe, but it was just leaking out before
it ever made it to the end. And so we
realized together on this call that it
would be much more valuable to the
business to build reactivation systems,
to build follow-up reminders on their
appointments so that people actually
started to show up more. And that's just
a perfect example of the reframe that
you have to do in order to really
diagnose what the true pain is. And
something interesting here is I think
about a slide that says this later too.
There's just a lot of power in silence.
So when I asked her the question of like
why did you book in this call? Like what
is truly the pain that you're feeling
here?
I stopped talking. She thought for a
couple seconds, responded, and then I
didn't respond yet because I I had a
feeling that that wasn't true. And when
you have that silent pause, they think
and they feel like they need to talk
more. And I'm not big into like the
sales tactics, right? Like I I don't
have the sales background, but that was
super powerful. I would pause and they
would just keep talking. And your job on
the discovery calls is to talk as much
as least as possible. Your job is to sit
there and listen. And that's how you're
able to diagnose. So that's one quick
example, right? But that happened all
the time. Now, if you guys were here
yesterday on the VIP VIP sessions and I
came around to the table, some of us dug
into this, some of us didn't, but there
are two questions that I love to ask
business owners or even your own
business, right? Like if you're trying
to help automate your own business and
remove constraints, that [snorts] works
super super well, especially when you
pair it with silence. So, the first one
is if a business is
supply constraint, if you had 10x the
business tomorrow, what would break
first? You ask them that and then you
just be quiet because they'll think
about the flow in chronological order
from start to finish. And the key word
there that I put in all caps is first
because whatever breaks first is the
first clog. Now, whenever you diagnose
and you fix that first clog, there's
going to be another one. There always
is. And that's the beauty of it and
that's how you get on a retainer because
you just keep solving constraints and
you keep scaling the business. So that's
really good. If there's supply
constraint, if they're demand
constraint, you basically just flip it.
You say, "What would you do to 10x the
business coming in tomorrow? How do you
get 10x the amount of water into your
pipe tomorrow?" So, whatever they're
already doing to get leads or maybe
they're not doing anything to get leads,
building systems to support that
initiative. And
that doesn't sometimes what you'll
realize is as an AI consultant is what
like a lot of us are calling it right
now. Your job is just as much to tell
them, hey, this is the problem that I'm
seeing and we can solve this with no AI.
So, sometimes the problem could be it's
a very service-based business. they're
supply constrained and so the key is to
just hire more people. Now, yeah, maybe
you could come in here and say, you know
what, let's build you some recruiting
agents and some screening agents. That
helps the hiring process. That removes
that constraint. But that's a really
great way to think about it as well is
that an AI consultant or someone that's
AI native, it doesn't mean that you use
AI for everything. It means that you
know just as well when not to use AI
because that perspective is even more
valuable in a world where AI is being
shoved down everyone's throats
and then you just be silent.
Okay. So, moving on to the second one
here, we've got the KPI.
So, the whole idea here is that you
before you accept any payment, you want
to choose one number that you're trying
to move and you're not choosing this
number, you're choosing it with the
stakeholder.
If you think back to that example
earlier where the business owner said to
me, "Hey, we're not getting the value we
paid for. It's because we didn't do well
all of these things but this one very
specifically because I had no way to
prove that a personal assistant was
helping his business. He came to me his
pain was I feel busy. What is the
solution in my mind? A personal
assistant. When we really dug into it,
the reason he was so busy is because he
was handwriting all his proposals. So
the better automation there would have
been for me to help him build an AI
agent that would automate the proposals
or at least get them 90% of the way
there. He checks it, he approves it. If
we would have aligned on a number
beforehand, then I know what I'm working
towards. I know the result that I'm
trying to drive for the business
because productivity is really
interesting.
Productivity is actually moving the
needle. And you can't move the needle if
you don't know what you're trying to
move it towards. Because a lot of us
feel like you might have had a day where
you sat down on your at your desk all
day, eight hours straight, let's say.
But maybe you watch a lot of YouTube
tutorials. Maybe you played around with
image generation for an hour and you
felt productive because you know you you
clock off and you you sat there for
eight hours. But how many of those hours
were you actually doing? What you need
to do to move that number forward? And
for us, you know, a lot of us, you know,
it's a business, so there's a lot of
different north stars. But knowing what
you're building towards that quarter or
that day or whatever it is helps you
actually be a lot more productive. And
if your agents know your goals, then
they can help you plan your days better
to be more productive. So something that
I would like to ask is, okay, let's say
we've scoped it down. We've we
understand the constraint and I forget
the example I use. Um,
anyways, let's say we we've scoped it
down to a certain automation, then I
could ask, "In a perfect world, what
does this look like for your business?
If we push this into production and it's
working perfectly, what do you want to
see?" And from there, you try to drill
into one certain metric. So maybe it is
an AI agent that sets appointments.
[clears throat] Maybe they say, "Okay,
yeah, I mean, right now we're getting
like five appointments a week from our
manual setters." In a perfect world, our
manual setters have those 10 hours a
week back to do other things and we're
booking in like 10 appointments a week.
And so now I know exactly what is a
success to them. So there's that's
completely objective. I can go work
towards that and I can prove that. So if
someone says to me, "Hey, we're not
getting the value we paid for. Look at
the scope. This is what we agreed on.
This you said that you wanted 10
appointments a week from this automation
and I objectively delivered that to
you." I probably would say a little bit
nicer though. Okay. So that's a
trackable and objective metric because a
lot of this stuff is very subjective. I
want a personal AI assistant so I can
feel more productive, so I feel less
busy. There's no way that I can actually
prove that. There's no way I can prove
to the business owner that he is now
less busy because of what I built. So,
they can't be subjective. So, like I
said, you have a baseline like five
weekly appointments. You've got a target
like 12 weekly appointments. And now you
know what you're working towards. Of
course, you're going to have to leverage
some of their expertise because if you
know not much about the process and you
try to set a baseline target of like,
you know, 35 appointments a week, that's
very tough and now you're not going to
be able to prove that.
But the idea is that each automation is
having something to work towards. And
like I said, if this is not you working
with a client, before you go out and
decide to dedicate some some of your own
internal resources or budget to a
project, you should probably figure out
what is that one metric you want to
move. A lot of times there are, you
know, it it drips into other metrics
too, but if you can choose one, it makes
the decision a lot easier. And then you
can figure out how is that actually
impacting the bottom line of the
business.
And that's how you prove, like I said,
that your automation helped.
Okay. Okay, the third piece now is on
the pricing side. Now, this is really
interesting.
I really don't think there's like a
standard universal right way to price.
Everyone's doing it a bit differently.
Even the big firms are changing up their
pricing. I've tried almost everything
that you could think of. I've tried
performance-based. I've t hourly. I've
tried retainers on hourly. I've tried
value based. I've tried just lots of
stuff.
Um the way I feel is that you should not
be charging hourly. I think that a lot
of people when they're getting started,
I hear, you know, I keep getting nos to
my price. I hear that there's imposter
syndrome. And so, I think hourly to
start is a really good way to get your
foot in the door and win some trust or
even start free. I think it's a really
good way to start, but I don't think you
should be building a business around
your hourly pricing. And it's it's
really simple and especially if you
start to think about the way that AI is
supposed to make us do more in less
time. So, it's all about the incentives.
All right, real quick, guys. I mentioned
this at the end of the presentation, but
I attached this completely free PDF,
which is like a 30-page resource on
pricing your AI solutions, which you can
access for completely free inside of my
free school community. The link for that
is down in the description. You just hop
in there, you'll click on all YouTube
resources, and you'll find that pricing
masterclass guide in there. So, if you
want it, it's there. Let's get back to
the video. Let's say you've got two
developers on your team and you're
providing services to businesses. You've
got one developer named Sarah and she's
a killer. She gets something done in 1
hour and you've got another developer
named Dan. He's good but he's a little
slower, three hours. And let's say for
the sake of the example, they produce
the exact same quality of solution. You
would then bill for Sarah's work, your
better developer, you would bill $150 to
the client or I don't know, however you
want to you get the point, right? $150.
And now Dan, because he took three
hours, you get more money. And those
incentives are completely backwards. Why
would you make more money for moving
slower and on a worse developer? Right?
It's all about incentives. It's all
about value based pricing. That this is
where we got to and this is what I
believe at the moment is the best way to
be doing this. And what that means is
yes,
the same automation could be different
amounts of valuable to different
businesses.
So you have to kind of take that into
account at least when you're going very
custom and you're consulting.
This is the way we did it, right? Oops.
A client should understand how they will
receive 10x their investment. That's
kind of the golden rule that I like to
to give, right? Because if you can walk
the stakeholder through the math,
whether that is a business you're trying
to help or whether that's you internally
trying to win a budget because you're
trying to, you know, build AI projects
in house, [snorts] you need to prove
that this investment of their money will
get them a 10x on it because that makes
it a really hard offer to say no to. So
the way that we would do this is
basically take 10% of the projected
annualized value of the price of the the
automation and that's a gear price. So
an example here, let's say you're
building a customer support agent and
the manual rep, the human rep spends
about 10 hours a week responding to
these tickets and this person is paid 40
bucks an hour. So the cost of the
business 40 bucks an hour for customer
support. 40 bucks an hour and the rep is
does this about 10 hours a week. That's
400 bucks a week. And if you annualize
that, that's about $2,100 over the
course of the year, the first year
projected annualized revenue.
And you take 10% of that. Now, 10% 20%,
I play with it a little bit, but let's
just say 10% for the sake of example.
That's $2,80
here. Because what you have to assume,
they don't always,
but you have to assume that they're
going to ask you,
can you please tell me how you got to
that number? Because a lot of people
will come in and they're kind of like
maybe they're shopping around, they're
trying to get a quote, they don't even
know how much to allocate a budget
towards. So if you assume that they're
going to ask you how did you get to that
number and you can confidently walk them
through the math and then you just be
silent and you don't devalue your work.
I'm kind of jumping ahead. I know I got
some slides here that cover this, but
anyways, you have to figure out what
does the manual process cost the
business. And so in this example, right,
I I was able to understand, okay, this
rep cost the business 40 bucks an hour.
They're not always going to tell you
salary. They're not always going to tell
you the hourly weight rate, but there's
other ways to figure out what does the
manual process cost the business. It
could be opportunity cost. Maybe they've
been having a different funnel or
tripwire that they've wanted to push out
for two quarters, but they haven't
because they are too busy, right?
There's there's other types of cost
besides just like the hourly cost. Maybe
you're building a voice appointment, uh,
a voice agent because the business
misses calls all the time. And every
missed call could potentially be, um, a
driveway, right? A driveway. And that
driveway could win the business $10,000.
So, there's other ways to figure out
what is the cost of the manual process.
You just have to ask good questions and
then be silent and listen,
like I said.
So, the key thing to remember here is
that cost doesn't justify price.
value justifies price. And
this was kind of tough for me to wrap my
head around at first because the first
thing I thought of as a very new
business owner was I need to protect my
margins here. I need to make sure that
I'm making this much money or this
percent of the deal and I'm keeping that
much to account for taxes to account
for, you know, what I have to pay my
employees to account for our API cost or
our service, whatever it is. I was
thinking about the margins. But I think
that obviously you still have to think
about the margins so you're not running
your business in the ground, but the
cost doesn't justify the price. And a
really good example that I heard from
Jonathan Stark who spoke at our event a
couple weeks ago, he was saying like
let's say you're paying someone to do
your lawn and you pay them a hundred
bucks for the lawn and he's been come,
you know, he's been coming to you for
for years. All of a sudden he buys a new
pickup truck and that's an expense to
his business. So he has higher costs on
his end and then he comes to you and
wants to charge you 200 for the exact
same job for the exact same lawn. That's
not something that people will typically
agree to because the cost doesn't
justify the price. The value justifies
the price.
So, like I said, you have to pretend and
you have to assume that as soon as you
say the price, they're going to come
back to you and ask, "How did you get
that number?" And then you just have to
walk them through the math. Now, what's
really important there is you don't want
to devalue your work. So, let's say
someone comes to you, you scope out the
right constraint, you figure out the
cost of the business, and you give them
a 10% number. Let's say it just comes
out to 15,000. And they were basically
planning$7,000
to be the maximum they were going to
spend on AI this quarter.
You don't want to get into this
negotiation of devaluing your work and
saying, "Ah, you know, this would be
15K, but for you, we'll do it for 7K."
You know, if you're really trying to get
your first client and you can get that,
then I would say do it reps over cash
upfront when you're getting started. But
you don't want to devalue your work.
What I would do in this situation is I
would say, "Okay,
this build, this solution is $15,000
worth of value to the business and you
have a $7,000 budget. Let's just drill
down the functionality a little bit and
treat this as a V1. we'll give you the
$7,000 worth of this automation and then
you know next quarter when you've got
the budget or once this automation's in
production and we're actively earning
you back time and money, then we'll look
at the next one. Because I think if you
if you set the impression right away
that you're willing to bump down your
price as soon as they push back, then
they're just going to keep doing that
and you don't want to devalue your work.
So that's pretty much what I wanted to
run through today. Um, obviously those
kind of three main things, there's a lot
more nuance to get into, which if you
guys want to chat more, I'd love to to
chat more. But think about this with
your own business. Um, actually, let's
just take let's just take one volunteer
real quick. Someone that Yeah. Um, is it
Allejo?
>> There we go. Tell us
in your business, you know what you're
driving towards, right?
>> Yeah.
>> At the highest level, are you supply
constrained or demand constrained?
>> Demand constraint. We [clears throat]
need more clients.
>> You need more clients. And how are you
currently getting those clients?
>> Uh content on YouTube. Uh it's not quite
converting. I'm doing webinars and out
of 20 people that have assisted webinars
over two months,
>> uh we've gotten zero appointment set.
>> Okay. So,
if you wanted to have 10x the amount of
business tomorrow, what would you have
to do?
>> Uh probably 10x the content.
>> Mhm. 10x the content. uh seems crazy but
the methods that I see today very
helpful.
>> Yeah, volume negates luck, right? But
you want to 10x the content without
decreasing the the quality of course. So
in this case,
obviously there's a lot more to dive
into here, but you know the way that
you're kind of you know your top of
funnel. What does it seem like you
should be focusing on automating when
you get home in a couple days or next
week?
Um the problems that I have heard on the
sales calls uh turning those into a
video.
>> Okay.
>> Uh that one is huge is I like forget
what we talked about
>> and maybe focus on something in the
sales call but I miss something else
that they said that is an actual problem
with their business.
>> Totally. And do you know how you could
automate that?
>> Now I do.
>> There we go. Um now something I saw I
remember talking to you about was the
grill me skill, right? Yeah,
>> if you guys don't know the grill me
skill, I mean, it's a very simple
prompt. Essentially, just at the end of
of questions, ask the AI to interview
you relentlessly about this topic
because what that does is it gets all of
the subject matter expertise in your
head into the AIOS that you're building.
Because once you give it all of that
nuance, it's able to build an automation
out of that so much better because the
way that you would kind of create these
AI agents to to uh, you know,
operationalize that process is different
than someone else might. So,
Obviously, that was a really quick
example. Thank you, Aljo. I appreciate
the the participation there. But just
constantly be asking yourself like what
is the actual constraint? You know, how
do we 10x the business? How do we
actually look through the flow of the
pipe and the water and figure out where
the clog is or where the leak is and
then just directly attack that? And so,
like I said earlier,
when we were working with businesses, we
would always start with our foot in the
door with one project on a value based
uh project fee. And from there, we
started to explain to them,
we are seeing all of these other clogs
because once we've removed this
constraint, there's another one. And
that's a good thing because still you're
getting more water through. And that's
how you're able to get on the retainer
because not only did you
find the right constraint, you also
chose a number beforehand so you can
objectively prove to them the automation
helped their business. And then you
price it in a way where it was a
no-brainer for them to say yes. And then
guess what? after you push it into
production, you come back one month, two
months, 3 months later and you show them
that number and now you're able to
justify asking for that retainer and to
just say, "Hey, you know, we can move a
lot quicker if we're not always doing
the scoping and we're not always
figuring out pricing, if we can just
work more and just keep attacking those
constraints." And that's the only way
that the business is truly going to
grow. So, that's pretty much what I want
to talk to you guys about today. I have
a full pricing guide. This is like a 29
30 page doc um kind of just like about
what I talked about today on the
valuebased pricing and some stuff like
that. Um so go ahead and scan that and
grab that doc. I'm sure we can include
it in the the resources later as well if
you miss it. But yeah, thank you guys so
much. It's been an awesome day and yeah,
let's let's have some dinner.
>> [applause]